{"front" : "The practice of collecting and analyzing data in large quantities" , "back" : "Statistics"}
{"front" : "Values such as counts, ratings, measurements, or opinions that are gathered to answer questions" , "back" : "Data"}
{"front" : "A value that represents the evening out of the values in a set of data" , "back" : "Mean"}
{"front" : "The number that is the midpoint of a set of data" , "back" : "Median"}
{"front" : "The data value that occurs the most", "back" : "Mode"}
{"front" : "The difference between the least value and the greatest value in a data set", "back" : "Range"}
{"front" : "A break or opening", "back" : "Gap"}
{"front" : "The arrangement of values in a set", "back" : "Distribution"}
{"front" : "Data that is close together", "back" : "Cluster"}
{"front" : "Being a the point of maximum frequency, intensity, use, etc", "back" : "Peak"}
{"front" : "One of the values that divides the distribution of the variable into four groups having equal frequencies", "back" : "Quartiles"}
{"front" : "A value that lies far from the center of a distribution", "back" : "Outlier"}
{"front" : "Asymmetry in a frequency distribution", "back" : "Skewed"}
{"front" : "Degree to which data are spread out around a center value", "back" : "Variability"}
{"front" : "Characterized by or exhibiting symmetry; well-proportioned, as a body or whole; regular in form or arrangement or corresponding parts", "back" : "Symmetrical"}